let questions=[
    {
        question : "Q.1. In 2009 Indian Premier League who got the title of Player of the series?",
        answer:"Adam Gilchrist",
        options: [ 
            "Adam Gilchrist",
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Robin Uthappa",
            "Shane Watson"
        ]
    },

    {
        question:"Q.2. Which team won the IPL (2009)?",
        answer:"Deccan Chargers",
        options: [
            "Deccan Chargers",
            "Chennai Super Kings",
            "Kolkata Knight Riders",
            "Delhi Daredevils"
        ]
    },

    {
        question:"Q.3. Which player scored most runs in IPL (2009)?",
        answer:"Sachin Tendulkar",
        options: [
            "Sanath Jaysuriya",
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Matthew Hayden",
            "Virender Sehwag"
        ]
    },


    {
        question:"Q.4. Which cricketer has bowled the most number of dot balls in the IPL??",
        answer:"Praveen Kumar",
        options: [
            "Praveen Kumar",
            "Lasith Malinga",
            "Harbhajan Singh",
            "Sunil Narine"
        ]
    },

    {
        question:"Q.5. Which company replaced DLF as the new title sponsor in 2013 IPL?",
        answer:"PepsiCo",
        options: [
            "PepsiCo",
            "Hindustan Unilever",
            "Nokia",
            "Patanjali"
        ]
    },

    {
        question:"Q.6. Which International star performed in the opening ceremony of 2013 IPL?",
        answer:"Pitbull",
        options: [
            "Jennifer Lopez",
            "Akon",
            "Pitbull",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },

    {
        question:"Q.7. Which team won the 2014 Indian Premier League tournament?",
        answer:"Kolkata Knight Riders",
        options: [
            "Kolkata Knight Riders",
            "Chennai Super Kings",
            "Deccan Chargers",
            "Royal Challengers Bangalore"
        ]
    },

    {
        question:"Q.8. Which team won Indian Premier League 2010?",
        answer:"Chennai Super Kings",
        options: [
            "Chennai Super Kings",
            "Kolkata Knight Riders",
            "Deccan Chargers",
            "Delhi Daredevils"
        ]
    },

    {
        question:"Q.9. Who hit the first century of IPL 2012?",
        answer:"Ajinkya Rahane",
        options: [
            "Adam Gilchrist",
            "Ajinkya Rahane",
            "Virat Kohli",
            "Ambati Rayudu"
        ]
    },

    {
        question:"Q.10. Who holds the infamous record of most number of ducks in IPL 2012?",
        answer:"Manish Pandey",
        options: [
            "Manish Pandey",
            "Munaf Patel",
            "Morne Morkel",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },

];